Titled photographs
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Bluebells, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Passion Play - The Entombment of Christ, 1910; 21; 49; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Passion Play - Risen Christ and Mary Magdalene, 1910; 22; 51; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Character study, Brigitta’s Smile, circa 1900-1920; 23; 1035; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Queen Mary, circa 1900-1920; 24; 1504; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Portrait - Moore, circa 1900-1920; 25; 2439; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Statuary, Water Babies, circa 1900-1920; 26; 13464; 3x4 b&w (Box 1453)
  - Ancient Egypt Prince Chariot of the XVIII Dynasty, circa 1900-1920; 27; 27774; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - La Belle Jardiniere by Raphael, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Venus and Adonis by Francesco Albani, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Perdita by Gainsborough, Wallace collection, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Spaniels of King Charles’s Breed by Landseer, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - The Syndics of the Clothmakers’ Guild (de Staalmeesters) by Rembrandt, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - School of Anatomy by Rembrandt, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Charity by Andrea del Sarto, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Mona Lisa by Leonardo da Vinci, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  - Portraits - William Shakespeare, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1453)
  Box 1454
- Titled photographs, 2.1.2.12.1
  - Portraits - Robert Burns, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Portraits ­- St. Patrick, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Portraits - The King of England, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Champagne Girl, Louvre, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Dr. James Carroll, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Dr. Spooner, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Pottery of cliff dweller, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Ancient Chinese coins, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Typical Turkish man, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Top of the RMS Lusitania, circa 1904-1915; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Sjursen[?] Fall, circa 1900-1920; 11; 41; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - A buffalo head, circa 1900-1920; 12; 98; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - A park deer, circa 1900-1920; 13; 99; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - A park bear, circa 1900-1920; 14; 100; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Wheat stacks, Dale, circa 1900-1920; 15; 141; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Cottage at Millshire, circa 1900-1920; 16; 401; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Costumes, Tuscan Contadina, circa 1900-1920; 17; 687; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Cedres du Liban, circa 1900-1920; 18; 1201; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Newhaven fishwives, circa 1900-1920; 19; 12334; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Sweet corn field, circa 1900-1920; 20; 34463; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Sheep in Franklin Park, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Blohm[?] and Uss[?], circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Market and Custom House, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Mayor’s house, Racobeth, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Avenue in Lekland[?], circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Tower, mountains, two men in foreground, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - Interior, first floor of Hope House, south, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - One of Baghdad’s ancient gates [National Geographic Society], circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - One of Baghdad’s ancient gates [National Geographic Society], circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1454)
  - The tomb of Zobeida, the favorite wife of Harun-al-Rashad, near Baghdad [National Geographic Society], circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1454)